var title = 'Traduza para grego.';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "101",
   answer: ["εκατόν ένα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "130",
   answer: ["εκατόν τριάντα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "200",
   answer: ["διακόσια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "300",
   answer: ["τριακόσια", "τρακόσια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "400",
   answer: ["τετρακόσια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "500",
   answer: ["πεντακόσια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "600",
   answer: ["εξακόσια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "700",
   answer: ["εφτακόσια", "επτακόσια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "800",
   answer: ["οχτακόσια", "οκτακόσια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "900",
   answer: ["εννιακόσια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "1000",
   answer: ["χίλια", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];